{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes W, V, E, J and directed edges W->V, W->J, V->J, W->E, V->E, E->J.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "88823235", "sid": 0, "question": "Find all directed paths from node V to node J.", "answer": "V->J, V->E->J", "question_type": "FA", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes W, V, E, J and directed edges W->V, W->J, V->J, W->E, V->E, E->J.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "88823235", "sid": 1, "question": "How many directed paths are there from E to J?", "answer": "1", "question_type": "HM", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes W, V, E, J and directed edges W->V, W->J, V->J, W->E, V->E, E->J.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "88823235", "sid": 2, "question": "Is V<-W->J<-E a directed path from V to E?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes W, V, E, J and directed edges W->V, W->J, V->J, W->E, V->E, E->J.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "88823235", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following is a directed path from W to E?\nA. W->J<-E\nB. W->J<-V->E\nC. W->V->J<-E\nD. W->E", "answer": "D", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes W, V, E, J and directed edges W->V, W->J, V->J, W->E, V->E, E->J.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "88823235", "sid": 4, "question": "Is there a directed path from V to W?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "EX", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes H, O, W, Y and directed edges O->Y, W->Y, O->W, H->O, H->Y.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "67564179", "sid": 0, "question": "Find all directed paths from node H to node O.", "answer": "H->O", "question_type": "FA", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes H, O, W, Y and directed edges O->Y, W->Y, O->W, H->O, H->Y.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "67564179", "sid": 1, "question": "How many directed paths are there from W to O?", "answer": "0", "question_type": "HM", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes H, O, W, Y and directed edges O->Y, W->Y, O->W, H->O, H->Y.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "67564179", "sid": 2, "question": "Is H->Y<-O a directed path from H to O?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes H, O, W, Y and directed edges O->Y, W->Y, O->W, H->O, H->Y.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "67564179", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following is a directed path from H to W?\nA. H->Y<-O->W\nB. H->O->W\nC. H->O->Y<-W\nD. H->Y<-W", "answer": "B", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes H, O, W, Y and directed edges O->Y, W->Y, O->W, H->O, H->Y.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "67564179", "sid": 4, "question": "Is there a directed path from W to H?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "EX", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes X, H, E, D, A and directed edges H->E, X->A, X->H, E->A, H->A, X->D, D->A, E->D.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "41337709", "sid": 0, "question": "Find all directed paths from node H to node A.", "answer": "H->A, H->E->A, H->E->D->A", "question_type": "FA", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes X, H, E, D, A and directed edges H->E, X->A, X->H, E->A, H->A, X->D, D->A, E->D.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "41337709", "sid": 1, "question": "How many directed paths are there from E to H?", "answer": "0", "question_type": "HM", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes X, H, E, D, A and directed edges H->E, X->A, X->H, E->A, H->A, X->D, D->A, E->D.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "41337709", "sid": 2, "question": "Is X->D<-E a directed path from X to E?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes X, H, E, D, A and directed edges H->E, X->A, X->H, E->A, H->A, X->D, D->A, E->D.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "41337709", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following is a directed path from X to E?\nA. X->H->E\nB. X->A<-D<-E\nC. X->H->A<-D<-E\nD. X->H->A<-E", "answer": "A", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes X, H, E, D, A and directed edges H->E, X->A, X->H, E->A, H->A, X->D, D->A, E->D.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "41337709", "sid": 4, "question": "Is there a directed path from A to H?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "EX", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes I, V, S, D, Y and directed edges S->D, I->S, S->Y, D->Y, V->Y, I->Y, V->S, I->D, I->V.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "25516600", "sid": 0, "question": "Find all directed paths from node I to node S.", "answer": "I->S, I->V->S", "question_type": "FA", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes I, V, S, D, Y and directed edges S->D, I->S, S->Y, D->Y, V->Y, I->Y, V->S, I->D, I->V.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "25516600", "sid": 1, "question": "How many directed paths are there from I to V?", "answer": "1", "question_type": "HM", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes I, V, S, D, Y and directed edges S->D, I->S, S->Y, D->Y, V->Y, I->Y, V->S, I->D, I->V.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "25516600", "sid": 2, "question": "Is I->V->S->D->Y a directed path from I to Y?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes I, V, S, D, Y and directed edges S->D, I->S, S->Y, D->Y, V->Y, I->Y, V->S, I->D, I->V.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "25516600", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following is a directed path from S to D?\nA. S<-I->Y<-D\nB. S->D\nC. S<-V<-I->D\nD. S<-V<-I->Y<-D", "answer": "B", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes I, V, S, D, Y and directed edges S->D, I->S, S->Y, D->Y, V->Y, I->Y, V->S, I->D, I->V.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "25516600", "sid": 4, "question": "Is there a directed path from D to V?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "EX", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes X, W, P, N, B, T and directed edges W->N, X->P, P->N, P->B, W->P, W->T, B->T, N->T.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "48510845", "sid": 0, "question": "Find all directed paths from node P to node T.", "answer": "P->B->T, P->N->T", "question_type": "FA", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes X, W, P, N, B, T and directed edges W->N, X->P, P->N, P->B, W->P, W->T, B->T, N->T.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "48510845", "sid": 1, "question": "How many directed paths are there from W to B?", "answer": "1", "question_type": "HM", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes X, W, P, N, B, T and directed edges W->N, X->P, P->N, P->B, W->P, W->T, B->T, N->T.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "48510845", "sid": 2, "question": "Is X->P->N a directed path from X to N?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes X, W, P, N, B, T and directed edges W->N, X->P, P->N, P->B, W->P, W->T, B->T, N->T.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "48510845", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following is a directed path from X to N?\nA. X->P<-W->N\nB. X->P->N\nC. X->P->B->T<-W->N\nD. X->P<-W->T<-N", "answer": "B", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes X, W, P, N, B, T and directed edges W->N, X->P, P->N, P->B, W->P, W->T, B->T, N->T.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "48510845", "sid": 4, "question": "Is there a directed path from X to N?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "EX", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes W, P, U, X, J, B and directed edges W->B, P->J, W->U, X->J, W->J, U->B, P->X, W->X, U->X, U->J, W->P, P->B.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "91874812", "sid": 0, "question": "Find all directed paths from node U to node X.", "answer": "U->X", "question_type": "FA", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes W, P, U, X, J, B and directed edges W->B, P->J, W->U, X->J, W->J, U->B, P->X, W->X, U->X, U->J, W->P, P->B.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "91874812", "sid": 1, "question": "How many directed paths are there from U to B?", "answer": "1", "question_type": "HM", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes W, P, U, X, J, B and directed edges W->B, P->J, W->U, X->J, W->J, U->B, P->X, W->X, U->X, U->J, W->P, P->B.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "91874812", "sid": 2, "question": "Is W->U->B a directed path from W to B?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes W, P, U, X, J, B and directed edges W->B, P->J, W->U, X->J, W->J, U->B, P->X, W->X, U->X, U->J, W->P, P->B.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "91874812", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following is a directed path from U to B?\nA. U->B\nB. U<-W->P->B\nC. U->J<-W->B\nD. U<-W->B", "answer": "A", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes W, P, U, X, J, B and directed edges W->B, P->J, W->U, X->J, W->J, U->B, P->X, W->X, U->X, U->J, W->P, P->B.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "91874812", "sid": 4, "question": "Is there a directed path from W to B?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "EX", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes A, V, F, X, G, C, H and directed edges C->H, X->H, A->C, A->V, F->H, X->G, A->X, V->C, F->X.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "68756387", "sid": 0, "question": "Find all directed paths from node V to node C.", "answer": "V->C", "question_type": "FA", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes A, V, F, X, G, C, H and directed edges C->H, X->H, A->C, A->V, F->H, X->G, A->X, V->C, F->X.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "68756387", "sid": 1, "question": "How many directed paths are there from A to F?", "answer": "0", "question_type": "HM", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes A, V, F, X, G, C, H and directed edges C->H, X->H, A->C, A->V, F->H, X->G, A->X, V->C, F->X.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "68756387", "sid": 2, "question": "Is V->C->H a directed path from V to H?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes A, V, F, X, G, C, H and directed edges C->H, X->H, A->C, A->V, F->H, X->G, A->X, V->C, F->X.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "68756387", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following is a directed path from V to H?\nA. V->C<-A->X<-F->H\nB. V->C->H\nC. V<-A->C->H\nD. V<-A->X->H", "answer": "B", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes A, V, F, X, G, C, H and directed edges C->H, X->H, A->C, A->V, F->H, X->G, A->X, V->C, F->X.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "68756387", "sid": 4, "question": "Is there a directed path from C to H?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "EX", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes P, U, Q, F, W, A, S and directed edges U->A, P->W, U->S, W->A, U->Q, F->S, Q->A, W->S, P->A, U->W, Q->F.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "64045072", "sid": 0, "question": "Find all directed paths from node U to node W.", "answer": "U->W", "question_type": "FA", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes P, U, Q, F, W, A, S and directed edges U->A, P->W, U->S, W->A, U->Q, F->S, Q->A, W->S, P->A, U->W, Q->F.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "64045072", "sid": 1, "question": "How many directed paths are there from P to F?", "answer": "0", "question_type": "HM", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes P, U, Q, F, W, A, S and directed edges U->A, P->W, U->S, W->A, U->Q, F->S, Q->A, W->S, P->A, U->W, Q->F.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "64045072", "sid": 2, "question": "Is Q<-U->W->A a directed path from Q to A?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes P, U, Q, F, W, A, S and directed edges U->A, P->W, U->S, W->A, U->Q, F->S, Q->A, W->S, P->A, U->W, Q->F.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "64045072", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following is a directed path from U to A?\nA. U->S<-F<-Q->A\nB. U->W->A\nC. U->Q->F->S<-W<-P->A\nD. U->W->S<-F<-Q->A", "answer": "B", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes P, U, Q, F, W, A, S and directed edges U->A, P->W, U->S, W->A, U->Q, F->S, Q->A, W->S, P->A, U->W, Q->F.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "64045072", "sid": 4, "question": "Is there a directed path from S to P?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "EX", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes W, X, H, Z, M, E, B, K and directed edges M->K, W->X, X->Z, X->M, W->B, X->E, X->H, M->B, Z->K.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "98075372", "sid": 0, "question": "Find all directed paths from node W to node M.", "answer": "W->X->M", "question_type": "FA", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes W, X, H, Z, M, E, B, K and directed edges M->K, W->X, X->Z, X->M, W->B, X->E, X->H, M->B, Z->K.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "98075372", "sid": 1, "question": "How many directed paths are there from Z to W?", "answer": "0", "question_type": "HM", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes W, X, H, Z, M, E, B, K and directed edges M->K, W->X, X->Z, X->M, W->B, X->E, X->H, M->B, Z->K.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "98075372", "sid": 2, "question": "Is W->X->E a directed path from W to E?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes W, X, H, Z, M, E, B, K and directed edges M->K, W->X, X->Z, X->M, W->B, X->E, X->H, M->B, Z->K.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "98075372", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following is a directed path from W to Z?\nA. W->X->Z\nB. W->X->M->K<-Z\nC. W->B<-M->K<-Z\nD. W->B<-M<-X->Z", "answer": "A", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes W, X, H, Z, M, E, B, K and directed edges M->K, W->X, X->Z, X->M, W->B, X->E, X->H, M->B, Z->K.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "98075372", "sid": 4, "question": "Is there a directed path from H to X?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "EX", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes V, N, G, Z, C, T, U, R and directed edges N->Z, Z->U, V->R, C->T, U->R, Z->T, G->T, N->U, C->U, V->G, V->U, N->T.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "83287041", "sid": 0, "question": "Find all directed paths from node U to node R.", "answer": "U->R", "question_type": "FA", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes V, N, G, Z, C, T, U, R and directed edges N->Z, Z->U, V->R, C->T, U->R, Z->T, G->T, N->U, C->U, V->G, V->U, N->T.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "83287041", "sid": 1, "question": "How many directed paths are there from V to U?", "answer": "1", "question_type": "HM", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes V, N, G, Z, C, T, U, R and directed edges N->Z, Z->U, V->R, C->T, U->R, Z->T, G->T, N->U, C->U, V->G, V->U, N->T.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "83287041", "sid": 2, "question": "Is G<-V->R<-U<-C->T a directed path from G to T?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes V, N, G, Z, C, T, U, R and directed edges N->Z, Z->U, V->R, C->T, U->R, Z->T, G->T, N->U, C->U, V->G, V->U, N->T.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "83287041", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following is a directed path from V to R?\nA. V->G->T<-C->U->R\nB. V->G->T<-Z<-N->U->R\nC. V->G->T<-N->Z->U->R\nD. V->U->R", "answer": "D", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes V, N, G, Z, C, T, U, R and directed edges N->Z, Z->U, V->R, C->T, U->R, Z->T, G->T, N->U, C->U, V->G, V->U, N->T.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "83287041", "sid": 4, "question": "Is there a directed path from C to T?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "EX", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes J, B, C, Z, Y, R, M, S, H and directed edges R->M, B->S, B->Y, C->R, C->S, S->H, C->M, C->H, Z->M, J->Y, Z->R, J->S.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "40551991", "sid": 0, "question": "Find all directed paths from node C to node R.", "answer": "C->R", "question_type": "FA", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes J, B, C, Z, Y, R, M, S, H and directed edges R->M, B->S, B->Y, C->R, C->S, S->H, C->M, C->H, Z->M, J->Y, Z->R, J->S.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "40551991", "sid": 1, "question": "How many directed paths are there from Z to Y?", "answer": "0", "question_type": "HM", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes J, B, C, Z, Y, R, M, S, H and directed edges R->M, B->S, B->Y, C->R, C->S, S->H, C->M, C->H, Z->M, J->Y, Z->R, J->S.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "40551991", "sid": 2, "question": "Is C->M a directed path from C to M?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes J, B, C, Z, Y, R, M, S, H and directed edges R->M, B->S, B->Y, C->R, C->S, S->H, C->M, C->H, Z->M, J->Y, Z->R, J->S.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "40551991", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following is a directed path from J to H?\nA. J->S<-C->H\nB. J->S->H\nC. J->Y<-B->S->H\nD. J->Y<-B->S<-C->H", "answer": "B", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes J, B, C, Z, Y, R, M, S, H and directed edges R->M, B->S, B->Y, C->R, C->S, S->H, C->M, C->H, Z->M, J->Y, Z->R, J->S.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "40551991", "sid": 4, "question": "Is there a directed path from J to C?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "EX", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes P, W, F, Y, L, U, D, K, S and directed edges W->K, D->S, P->Y, L->D, F->D, P->L, D->K, Y->D, P->D, Y->L, W->U, P->S.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "63173785", "sid": 0, "question": "Find all directed paths from node Y to node K.", "answer": "Y->D->K, Y->L->D->K", "question_type": "FA", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes P, W, F, Y, L, U, D, K, S and directed edges W->K, D->S, P->Y, L->D, F->D, P->L, D->K, Y->D, P->D, Y->L, W->U, P->S.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "63173785", "sid": 1, "question": "How many directed paths are there from S to Y?", "answer": "0", "question_type": "HM", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes P, W, F, Y, L, U, D, K, S and directed edges W->K, D->S, P->Y, L->D, F->D, P->L, D->K, Y->D, P->D, Y->L, W->U, P->S.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "63173785", "sid": 2, "question": "Is L<-Y<-P->D->K a directed path from L to K?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes P, W, F, Y, L, U, D, K, S and directed edges W->K, D->S, P->Y, L->D, F->D, P->L, D->K, Y->D, P->D, Y->L, W->U, P->S.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "63173785", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following is a directed path from Y to S?\nA. Y->D<-P->S\nB. Y<-P->D->S\nC. Y->L<-P->S\nD. Y->L->D->S", "answer": "D", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes P, W, F, Y, L, U, D, K, S and directed edges W->K, D->S, P->Y, L->D, F->D, P->L, D->K, Y->D, P->D, Y->L, W->U, P->S.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "63173785", "sid": 4, "question": "Is there a directed path from U to Y?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "EX", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes B, F, C, K, directed edges B->C, B->K, F->K, C->K, F->C and bi-directed edges F<->C, C<->K.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "74846378", "sid": 0, "question": "Find all directed paths from node B to node C.", "answer": "B->C", "question_type": "FA", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes B, F, C, K, directed edges B->C, B->K, F->K, C->K, F->C and bi-directed edges F<->C, C<->K.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "74846378", "sid": 1, "question": "How many directed paths are there from C to F?", "answer": "0", "question_type": "HM", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes B, F, C, K, directed edges B->C, B->K, F->K, C->K, F->C and bi-directed edges F<->C, C<->K.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "74846378", "sid": 2, "question": "Is F->K<->C a directed path from F to C?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes B, F, C, K, directed edges B->C, B->K, F->K, C->K, F->C and bi-directed edges F<->C, C<->K.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "74846378", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following is a directed path from B to C?\nA. B->K<-C\nB. B->K<-F<->C\nC. B->C\nD. B->K<-F->C", "answer": "C", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes B, F, C, K, directed edges B->C, B->K, F->K, C->K, F->C and bi-directed edges F<->C, C<->K.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "74846378", "sid": 4, "question": "Is there a directed path from F to B?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "EX", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes U, Q, A, C, directed edges Q->C, U->A, Q->A, U->Q, U->C and bi-directed edges Q<->C.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "44013848", "sid": 0, "question": "Find all directed paths from node U to node A.", "answer": "U->A, U->Q->A", "question_type": "FA", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes U, Q, A, C, directed edges Q->C, U->A, Q->A, U->Q, U->C and bi-directed edges Q<->C.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "44013848", "sid": 1, "question": "How many directed paths are there from Q to C?", "answer": "1", "question_type": "HM", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes U, Q, A, C, directed edges Q->C, U->A, Q->A, U->Q, U->C and bi-directed edges Q<->C.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "44013848", "sid": 2, "question": "Is U->C<->Q->A a directed path from U to A?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes U, Q, A, C, directed edges Q->C, U->A, Q->A, U->Q, U->C and bi-directed edges Q<->C.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "44013848", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following is a directed path from Q to A?\nA. Q<-U->A\nB. Q<->C<-U->A\nC. Q->A\nD. Q->C<-U->A", "answer": "C", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes U, Q, A, C, directed edges Q->C, U->A, Q->A, U->Q, U->C and bi-directed edges Q<->C.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "44013848", "sid": 4, "question": "Is there a directed path from A to Q?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "EX", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes B, K, T, Z, D, directed edges B->D, T->Z, T->D, Z->D, K->T, B->K and bi-directed edges B<->T, Z<->D.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "23929624", "sid": 0, "question": "Find all directed paths from node B to node T.", "answer": "B->K->T", "question_type": "FA", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes B, K, T, Z, D, directed edges B->D, T->Z, T->D, Z->D, K->T, B->K and bi-directed edges B<->T, Z<->D.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "23929624", "sid": 1, "question": "How many directed paths are there from K to Z?", "answer": "1", "question_type": "HM", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes B, K, T, Z, D, directed edges B->D, T->Z, T->D, Z->D, K->T, B->K and bi-directed edges B<->T, Z<->D.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "23929624", "sid": 2, "question": "Is B->K->T->Z a directed path from B to Z?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes B, K, T, Z, D, directed edges B->D, T->Z, T->D, Z->D, K->T, B->K and bi-directed edges B<->T, Z<->D.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "23929624", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following is a directed path from T to Z?\nA. T<-K<-B->D<->Z\nB. T->D<-Z\nC. T->Z\nD. T<->B->D<->Z", "answer": "C", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes B, K, T, Z, D, directed edges B->D, T->Z, T->D, Z->D, K->T, B->K and bi-directed edges B<->T, Z<->D.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "23929624", "sid": 4, "question": "Is there a directed path from Z to D?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "EX", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes U, A, Q, F, N, directed edges Q->F, A->N, U->N, F->N, Q->N, U->A, U->F and bi-directed edges Q<->N, A<->N, A<->Q.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "60991070", "sid": 0, "question": "Find all directed paths from node Q to node F.", "answer": "Q->F", "question_type": "FA", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes U, A, Q, F, N, directed edges Q->F, A->N, U->N, F->N, Q->N, U->A, U->F and bi-directed edges Q<->N, A<->N, A<->Q.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "60991070", "sid": 1, "question": "How many directed paths are there from U to A?", "answer": "1", "question_type": "HM", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes U, A, Q, F, N, directed edges Q->F, A->N, U->N, F->N, Q->N, U->A, U->F and bi-directed edges Q<->N, A<->N, A<->Q.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "60991070", "sid": 2, "question": "Is Q->N<-U->F a directed path from Q to F?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes U, A, Q, F, N, directed edges Q->F, A->N, U->N, F->N, Q->N, U->A, U->F and bi-directed edges Q<->N, A<->N, A<->Q.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "60991070", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following is a directed path from U to F?\nA. U->N<-A<->Q->F\nB. U->F\nC. U->N<->Q->F\nD. U->N<->A<->Q->F", "answer": "B", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes U, A, Q, F, N, directed edges Q->F, A->N, U->N, F->N, Q->N, U->A, U->F and bi-directed edges Q<->N, A<->N, A<->Q.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "60991070", "sid": 4, "question": "Is there a directed path from Q to F?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "EX", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes B, N, O, Y, E, U, directed edges N->Y, N->O, B->U, Y->E, O->Y, B->Y, E->U and bi-directed edges N<->U, Y<->U, O<->E.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "39481900", "sid": 0, "question": "Find all directed paths from node O to node E.", "answer": "O->Y->E", "question_type": "FA", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes B, N, O, Y, E, U, directed edges N->Y, N->O, B->U, Y->E, O->Y, B->Y, E->U and bi-directed edges N<->U, Y<->U, O<->E.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "39481900", "sid": 1, "question": "How many directed paths are there from O to N?", "answer": "0", "question_type": "HM", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes B, N, O, Y, E, U, directed edges N->Y, N->O, B->U, Y->E, O->Y, B->Y, E->U and bi-directed edges N<->U, Y<->U, O<->E.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "39481900", "sid": 2, "question": "Is N->Y a directed path from N to Y?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes B, N, O, Y, E, U, directed edges N->Y, N->O, B->U, Y->E, O->Y, B->Y, E->U and bi-directed edges N<->U, Y<->U, O<->E.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "39481900", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following is a directed path from Y to U?\nA. Y<-B->U\nB. Y<-N<->U\nC. Y->E->U\nD. Y->E<->O<-N<->U", "answer": "C", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes B, N, O, Y, E, U, directed edges N->Y, N->O, B->U, Y->E, O->Y, B->Y, E->U and bi-directed edges N<->U, Y<->U, O<->E.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "39481900", "sid": 4, "question": "Is there a directed path from N to E?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "EX", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes T, M, Y, K, P, G, directed edges M->G, M->K, M->Y, Y->G, M->P, P->G, T->M, Y->K, K->P, Y->P and bi-directed edges T<->P, K<->G, P<->G, M<->P.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "55051698", "sid": 0, "question": "Find all directed paths from node P to node G.", "answer": "P->G", "question_type": "FA", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes T, M, Y, K, P, G, directed edges M->G, M->K, M->Y, Y->G, M->P, P->G, T->M, Y->K, K->P, Y->P and bi-directed edges T<->P, K<->G, P<->G, M<->P.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "55051698", "sid": 1, "question": "How many directed paths are there from P to K?", "answer": "0", "question_type": "HM", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes T, M, Y, K, P, G, directed edges M->G, M->K, M->Y, Y->G, M->P, P->G, T->M, Y->K, K->P, Y->P and bi-directed edges T<->P, K<->G, P<->G, M<->P.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "55051698", "sid": 2, "question": "Is Y->G<->P<-M->K a directed path from Y to K?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes T, M, Y, K, P, G, directed edges M->G, M->K, M->Y, Y->G, M->P, P->G, T->M, Y->K, K->P, Y->P and bi-directed edges T<->P, K<->G, P<->G, M<->P.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "55051698", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following is a directed path from T to P?\nA. T->M->Y->P\nB. T<->P\nC. T->M->Y->G<-P\nD. T->M->Y->K<->G<->P", "answer": "A", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes T, M, Y, K, P, G, directed edges M->G, M->K, M->Y, Y->G, M->P, P->G, T->M, Y->K, K->P, Y->P and bi-directed edges T<->P, K<->G, P<->G, M<->P.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "55051698", "sid": 4, "question": "Is there a directed path from T to P?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "EX", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes D, C, M, G, S, T, O, directed edges G->T, D->G, S->T, M->O, T->O, C->T, D->O, C->O, D->S, C->G, G->O and bi-directed edges S<->T, M<->O, T<->O, D<->G.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "48460263", "sid": 0, "question": "Find all directed paths from node D to node T.", "answer": "D->G->T, D->S->T", "question_type": "FA", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes D, C, M, G, S, T, O, directed edges G->T, D->G, S->T, M->O, T->O, C->T, D->O, C->O, D->S, C->G, G->O and bi-directed edges S<->T, M<->O, T<->O, D<->G.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "48460263", "sid": 1, "question": "How many directed paths are there from D to M?", "answer": "0", "question_type": "HM", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes D, C, M, G, S, T, O, directed edges G->T, D->G, S->T, M->O, T->O, C->T, D->O, C->O, D->S, C->G, G->O and bi-directed edges S<->T, M<->O, T<->O, D<->G.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "48460263", "sid": 2, "question": "Is M<->O a directed path from M to O?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes D, C, M, G, S, T, O, directed edges G->T, D->G, S->T, M->O, T->O, C->T, D->O, C->O, D->S, C->G, G->O and bi-directed edges S<->T, M<->O, T<->O, D<->G.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "48460263", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following is a directed path from C to G?\nA. C->O<-T<->S<-D->G\nB. C->O<-T<-S<-D->G\nC. C->T->O<-D->G\nD. C->G", "answer": "D", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes D, C, M, G, S, T, O, directed edges G->T, D->G, S->T, M->O, T->O, C->T, D->O, C->O, D->S, C->G, G->O and bi-directed edges S<->T, M<->O, T<->O, D<->G.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "48460263", "sid": 4, "question": "Is there a directed path from S to C?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "EX", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes T, U, L, Y, M, C, O, directed edges U->M, L->C, Y->O, T->O, M->C, U->C, L->M, U->O, T->M, Y->C, U->Y and bi-directed edges T<->U, M<->O, L<->O, U<->C.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "05204221", "sid": 0, "question": "Find all directed paths from node T to node M.", "answer": "T->M", "question_type": "FA", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes T, U, L, Y, M, C, O, directed edges U->M, L->C, Y->O, T->O, M->C, U->C, L->M, U->O, T->M, Y->C, U->Y and bi-directed edges T<->U, M<->O, L<->O, U<->C.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "05204221", "sid": 1, "question": "How many directed paths are there from C to T?", "answer": "0", "question_type": "HM", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes T, U, L, Y, M, C, O, directed edges U->M, L->C, Y->O, T->O, M->C, U->C, L->M, U->O, T->M, Y->C, U->Y and bi-directed edges T<->U, M<->O, L<->O, U<->C.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "05204221", "sid": 2, "question": "Is T->M<->O<-Y<-U->C a directed path from T to C?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes T, U, L, Y, M, C, O, directed edges U->M, L->C, Y->O, T->O, M->C, U->C, L->M, U->O, T->M, Y->C, U->Y and bi-directed edges T<->U, M<->O, L<->O, U<->C.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "05204221", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following is a directed path from L to M?\nA. L->C<-Y<-U->M\nB. L<->O<->M\nC. L->C<->U->Y->O<->M\nD. L->M", "answer": "D", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes T, U, L, Y, M, C, O, directed edges U->M, L->C, Y->O, T->O, M->C, U->C, L->M, U->O, T->M, Y->C, U->Y and bi-directed edges T<->U, M<->O, L<->O, U<->C.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "05204221", "sid": 4, "question": "Is there a directed path from Y to C?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "EX", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes B, U, G, V, T, D, M, E, directed edges V->E, U->D, B->G, V->T, U->V, M->E, T->D, T->M, V->M, G->T, D->M, U->M and bi-directed edges U<->E, V<->E, G<->M, G<->V, V<->T, M<->E.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "13847528", "sid": 0, "question": "Find all directed paths from node G to node M.", "answer": "G->T->M, G->T->D->M", "question_type": "FA", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes B, U, G, V, T, D, M, E, directed edges V->E, U->D, B->G, V->T, U->V, M->E, T->D, T->M, V->M, G->T, D->M, U->M and bi-directed edges U<->E, V<->E, G<->M, G<->V, V<->T, M<->E.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "13847528", "sid": 1, "question": "How many directed paths are there from D to V?", "answer": "0", "question_type": "HM", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes B, U, G, V, T, D, M, E, directed edges V->E, U->D, B->G, V->T, U->V, M->E, T->D, T->M, V->M, G->T, D->M, U->M and bi-directed edges U<->E, V<->E, G<->M, G<->V, V<->T, M<->E.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "13847528", "sid": 2, "question": "Is U->V->M->E a directed path from U to E?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes B, U, G, V, T, D, M, E, directed edges V->E, U->D, B->G, V->T, U->V, M->E, T->D, T->M, V->M, G->T, D->M, U->M and bi-directed edges U<->E, V<->E, G<->M, G<->V, V<->T, M<->E.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "13847528", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following is a directed path from G to T?\nA. G->T\nB. G<->V->E<->M<-D<-T\nC. G<->M<-V<-U->D<-T\nD. G<->V->E<-M<-U->D<-T", "answer": "A", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes B, U, G, V, T, D, M, E, directed edges V->E, U->D, B->G, V->T, U->V, M->E, T->D, T->M, V->M, G->T, D->M, U->M and bi-directed edges U<->E, V<->E, G<->M, G<->V, V<->T, M<->E.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "13847528", "sid": 4, "question": "Is there a directed path from M to V?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "EX", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes E, K, Q, C, D, G, T, J, directed edges Q->D, C->J, K->Q, K->C, Q->T, G->T, G->J, E->J, E->T and bi-directed edges K<->C.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "73653812", "sid": 0, "question": "Find all directed paths from node E to node T.", "answer": "E->T", "question_type": "FA", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes E, K, Q, C, D, G, T, J, directed edges Q->D, C->J, K->Q, K->C, Q->T, G->T, G->J, E->J, E->T and bi-directed edges K<->C.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "73653812", "sid": 1, "question": "How many directed paths are there from C to G?", "answer": "0", "question_type": "HM", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes E, K, Q, C, D, G, T, J, directed edges Q->D, C->J, K->Q, K->C, Q->T, G->T, G->J, E->J, E->T and bi-directed edges K<->C.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "73653812", "sid": 2, "question": "Is G->J<-E->T a directed path from G to T?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes E, K, Q, C, D, G, T, J, directed edges Q->D, C->J, K->Q, K->C, Q->T, G->T, G->J, E->J, E->T and bi-directed edges K<->C.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "73653812", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following is a directed path from Q to T?\nA. Q->T\nB. Q<-K<->C->J<-G->T\nC. Q<-K->C->J<-G->T\nD. Q<-K<->C->J<-E->T", "answer": "A", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes E, K, Q, C, D, G, T, J, directed edges Q->D, C->J, K->Q, K->C, Q->T, G->T, G->J, E->J, E->T and bi-directed edges K<->C.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "73653812", "sid": 4, "question": "Is there a directed path from E to Q?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "EX", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes J, F, N, O, K, I, V, Y, T, directed edges J->Y, O->K, J->V, J->N, V->Y, F->N, O->Y, V->T, O->T, N->O, I->V, J->I and bi-directed edges F<->N, J<->V, I<->Y, O<->I, N<->O.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "04274496", "sid": 0, "question": "Find all directed paths from node N to node Y.", "answer": "N->O->Y", "question_type": "FA", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes J, F, N, O, K, I, V, Y, T, directed edges J->Y, O->K, J->V, J->N, V->Y, F->N, O->Y, V->T, O->T, N->O, I->V, J->I and bi-directed edges F<->N, J<->V, I<->Y, O<->I, N<->O.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "04274496", "sid": 1, "question": "How many directed paths are there from Y to I?", "answer": "0", "question_type": "HM", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes J, F, N, O, K, I, V, Y, T, directed edges J->Y, O->K, J->V, J->N, V->Y, F->N, O->Y, V->T, O->T, N->O, I->V, J->I and bi-directed edges F<->N, J<->V, I<->Y, O<->I, N<->O.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "04274496", "sid": 2, "question": "Is J<->V<-I<->Y<-O<->N a directed path from J to N?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes J, F, N, O, K, I, V, Y, T, directed edges J->Y, O->K, J->V, J->N, V->Y, F->N, O->Y, V->T, O->T, N->O, I->V, J->I and bi-directed edges F<->N, J<->V, I<->Y, O<->I, N<->O.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "04274496", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following is a directed path from F to T?\nA. F<->N<->O->Y<-J->I->V->T\nB. F->N<-J->V<-I<->O->T\nC. F->N<-J->Y<-O->T\nD. F->N->O->T", "answer": "D", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes J, F, N, O, K, I, V, Y, T, directed edges J->Y, O->K, J->V, J->N, V->Y, F->N, O->Y, V->T, O->T, N->O, I->V, J->I and bi-directed edges F<->N, J<->V, I<->Y, O<->I, N<->O.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "04274496", "sid": 4, "question": "Is there a directed path from Y to V?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "EX", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes R, D, K, S, M, W, Z, P, B, directed edges Z->B, K->Z, R->D, K->S, D->P, D->W, K->P, S->B, P->B, K->M, M->Z, W->Z and bi-directed edges R<->Z, R<->W, W<->Z, K<->B.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "80545388", "sid": 0, "question": "Find all directed paths from node R to node W.", "answer": "R->D->W", "question_type": "FA", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes R, D, K, S, M, W, Z, P, B, directed edges Z->B, K->Z, R->D, K->S, D->P, D->W, K->P, S->B, P->B, K->M, M->Z, W->Z and bi-directed edges R<->Z, R<->W, W<->Z, K<->B.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "80545388", "sid": 1, "question": "How many directed paths are there from Z to R?", "answer": "0", "question_type": "HM", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes R, D, K, S, M, W, Z, P, B, directed edges Z->B, K->Z, R->D, K->S, D->P, D->W, K->P, S->B, P->B, K->M, M->Z, W->Z and bi-directed edges R<->Z, R<->W, W<->Z, K<->B.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "80545388", "sid": 2, "question": "Is K->Z->B a directed path from K to B?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes R, D, K, S, M, W, Z, P, B, directed edges Z->B, K->Z, R->D, K->S, D->P, D->W, K->P, S->B, P->B, K->M, M->Z, W->Z and bi-directed edges R<->Z, R<->W, W<->Z, K<->B.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "80545388", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following is a directed path from K to Z?\nA. K->M->Z\nB. K<->B<-P<-D->W<->Z\nC. K->P<-D<-R<->Z\nD. K->P<-D->W<->R<->Z", "answer": "A", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "directed_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes R, D, K, S, M, W, Z, P, B, directed edges Z->B, K->Z, R->D, K->S, D->P, D->W, K->P, S->B, P->B, K->M, M->Z, W->Z and bi-directed edges R<->Z, R<->W, W<->Z, K<->B.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "80545388", "sid": 4, "question": "Is there a directed path from W to P?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "EX", "task_type": "directed_path"}
